Guide to the Lillian Hoban Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Artwork and writings, 1961-1997; Series II; 14.38; (80 boxes)
  - Other works
    - Which Shoes To Choose?, poem with drawings, undated; cuid350 (Box 62 (Oversize))
- Posters, circa 1970-1994; Series III; 0.25; (1 box)
  - Everybody's Favorite Grade, 1989; cuid351 (Box 82 (Oversize))
  - Hooray For Lillian Hoban's Books, circa 1990; cuid352 (Box 82 (Oversize))
    Also includes original poster art
  - Prescription For A Healthy Child, circa 1970; cuid353 (Box 82 (Oversize))
  - Start Reading, 1991; cuid354 (Box 82 (Oversize))
  - Where Do The Animals Go When It Rains, 1994; cuid355 (Box 82 (Oversize))
- Audiovisual materials, 1968-1994; Series IV; 0.42; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Interviews with Russell and Lillian Hoban, Pathways Educational Series, Highwood Hills, 1979 May 1; cuid356; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099360175)
  - Grade 2 Letters to Mr. and Mrs. Hoban, 1968 May 7; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099360183)
    A note on the box of the audiotape reel reads: Dear Mrs. Hoban, The class and I would love to have you, your husband and your family visit us. A little bird told us you did stop in Lynn one time. The children could have a Ba[?] Parade. You might enjoy that. Please try. Sincerely, Frances Goddard
  - Unidentified, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099360191)
  - Dance reel of Lillian Hoban, who trained with Martha Graham disciple and danced professionally - 16mm sound print, undated; cuid357 (Box 83)
    16 mm film
  - Hello, Arthur! Volume II, featuring author and illustrator Lillian Hoban as she reads: Arthur's Honey Bear, Arthur's Prize Reader, Arthur's Funny Money. Produced by CRM Group, Melbourne, Florida, undated; GENMSS1199_0001; 1; 00:13:27 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002102317097)
    Copyright on the video reads: 1992
  - Arhur's Prize Reader, 1978, 1984; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099360209)
  - Mrs. Bush's Story Time: Thanksgiving Hour 2, 1994; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099360217)
  - The Trumpet Club, Authors on Tape: Lillian Hoban, 1991; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002099360225)
- Electronic media, circa 2000; Series V; 0.21; (1 box)
  Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - CD with material from Russell and Lillian Hoban., circa 2000; cuid360 (Box 84)
- Printed materials, 4.04; 5 boxes
  - Printed material, cuid361 (Box A)
  - Printed material, cuid362 (Box B)
  - Printed material, cuid363 (Box C)
  - Printed material, cuid364 (Box D)
  - Printed material, cuid365 (Box E)